gpsunderground.com 2015-06-13

# Contact Us - GPS Underground :: Your Tracks Guide

The Privacy policy below describes how GPSUnderground collects and uses information about its customers and website visitors (You or The Users).

## What information does GPSUnderground collect from its Users?

GPSUnderground collects different types of personally identifiable information in order to be able to provide its services to You. Such information may include but is not limited to name, mailing address, telephone numbers, email addresses, credit card information and other. Users provide all such information voluntarily through various order forms, email messages sent to GPSUnderground, LiveChat, telephone, etc.

. 

GPSUnderground also collects different types of non-personally identifiable information that may include referral URL's, Users' IP addresses, Users' use of website, information about the browsers used by the User, etc. Some of this information is collected through Cookies, which are small pieces of data that are sent to your browser from a web server and are stored on your computer's hard drive and help GPSUnderground identify you as the User. You have the choice to modify your browser and thus to reject the Company's cookies.

## How does GPSUnderground use the information it collects?

GPSUnderground uses all collected information primarily for provisioning the services you have ordered and providing you with ongoing User support. We may also use your information for sending periodic emails announcing important service changes, new features, technical issues updates and news, promotional activities, etc. You can decide NOT to receive such emails by replying to any of them with "Unsubscribe" in the subject. We may also use your information to send you SMS notifications in case of issues which may lead to service interruption of your account(s). User information is also used for improving GPSUnderground's business processes to make your overall user experience more rewarding. Your information can also be used for resolving ownership and other disputes and enforcing agreements between you and GPSUnderground.

## Does GPSUnderground disclose Users' information to third parties?

All personal information collected by GPSUnderground is treated as strictly confidential. We may disclose User's personal information if required by law. We may disclose part of Users' personal information to our business partners, independent contractors or other third parties when this is required in order to provide the services you have ordered. For example: your Credit card information may be provided for payment confirmation and verification to the partnering entity involved in processing your payment; the personal information of anyone who uses GPSUnderground's domain name registration services is available in the public WHOIS searches as required by the domain name registration regulations; your personal and business related information may be provide to the SSL certificate provider with whom GPSUnderground cooperates for providing you with the SSL certificate service, etc. The use of any data provided by GPSUnderground to these partnering service providers is governed by their own Privacy Policies and is beyond GPSUnderground's control.

## What does GPSUnderground do to prevent loss, misuse or alteration of Users information?

We guarantee that we strictly apply all industry standard security measures to protect your personal information. Such measures include without limitation: data encryption, password protected access to Users' personal information, limited access to the sensitive data, encrypted transfer of sensitive data submitted by the User through GPSUnderground's order forms, login forms etc. There may be security and privacy limitations, which are beyond GPSUnderground's control. By choosing to provide personal information to GPSUnderground you understand and agree that the security, integrity and privacy of your information cannot be 100% guaranteed.

GPSUnderground reserves the right to change this Privacy Policy at any time. Such changes will become effective and binding after their posting on the GPSUnderground.com website. You agree to regularly review this Privacy Policy for revisions and updates. By continuing to use GPSUnderground's services and website after any posted revision, you agree to those changes.

To report an incident of abuse, please [email us](http://gpsunderground.com/forum/Privacy-Policy.html).
